# Ali Hamza Ranjha

Front-End Developer

### Contact

#### **Phone**

0315-0524857

#### **Email**

hamzaranjha093@gmail.com

#### LinkedIn

www.linkedin.com/in/ali-hamza-ranjha

#### **GitHub**

https://github.com/alihamzaranjha007

#### **Portfolio**

https://alihamzaranjha007.github.io/portfolio/

# **Education**

2019-2023

### **Bachelor in Computer Science**

University of Gujrat sub-campus Mandi Bahauddin

CGPA: 3.28/4.0

2016-2018

### **Intermediate (FSc. Pre-Engineering)**

Govt. Graduate college Mandi Bahauddin

Marks: 694/1100

# **Skills**

- HTML
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript
- PHP
- SQLite
- Java
- XML
- Flutter
- Dart
- Illustrator
- Photoshop

# **About Me**

Front-End Developer with a passion for crafting visually stunning and highly responsive web and mobile app experiences. Have good understanding of design principles. Proficient in the latest web, mobile app technologies and frameworks, with a keen eye for design aesthetics.

# **Experience**

June 2023 - Sep 2023

CIT NAVTTC, Punjab Computer College, M.B.Din

### **Teacher**

I have taught CIT(web, software & Mobile application) course offered by NAVTTC which includes:

- Web Development: (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP and Bootstrap)
- Mobile App Development: Flutter

#### March 2023 - April 2023

Internship, Cybrox Solution M.B.Din

# Web Developer

- Created website **PhotoApp** using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and also used frameworks like Bootstraps for better responsive websites.
- Customized and managed shopify store in our final year project.

Dec 2022 - Sep 2023

### **Android and Flutter Development**

- I have created android applications using java and uploaded on my GitHub.
- Applications: Health file, Music Player app
- I have also created some small projects using flutter framework.

# **Final Year Project**

My FYP is Virtual Shirt try-on in which segmentation of person, cloth and style transfer used to style on target body.

# **Achievements**

- I have got 3rd position for my **Health File** android app in an exhibition (Rising Entrepreneur Exhibition) held in UOG by computer science department.
- I have Received Shield of honor as a Graphic Designer Head from MCS.

# References

- https://github.com/alihamzaranjha007/Music-Player
- https://github.com/alihamzaranjha007/Health-File
- https://github.com/alihamzaranjha007/photo-app